VOLKAN ALKAN



Personal

- Address
 Besiktas / Istanbul
- Phone number +90 (531) 428 97 38
- Email volkanalkan2001@hotmail.com
- Date of birth 27-08-2001
- Place of birth Izmir - Turkey
- website volkanalkan.org
- LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/volkanalkanoffic

Interests

- Piano (over 12 years Professional) / Guitar / Violin
- Volleyball / Basketball (played licensed in teams)
- Artificial Intelligence
- Research

Languages

Hello there, I am Volkan! I am 19 years old, a first year computer engineering student and a web developer. I have been involved in web development for over 1 year. Also, music has always been my companion. I am a professional pianist as well. Iwould like to change the future and shape it for the benefit of the people by using my past experiences. My ultimate goal is to be a beneficial individual to society and to ensure that people are. I want to work with determination so that my engineering knowledge and skills will be useful to our society. The projects that I will take advantage of my creativity will always be directed towards a better world.

Work experience

volkanalkan.org - Founder

Sep 2020 - Present

Izmir / Turkey

The main purpose of this project is to get closer to one of my goals, the plan of establishing a virtual company, to show myself by establishing a personal website.

Google Developer Students Club - Core Member Google DSC Bau, Istanbul / Turkey

Sep 2020 - Present

Developer Student Club Leads are passionate volunteer leaders at their university who are dedicated to helping their peers learn and connect. These Leads may be pursuing various degrees but have a good foundational knowledge of software development concepts. Google collaborates with DSC Leads once a year who are pursuing an undergraduate or graduate university degree and supports them as they start and grow their on-campus community.

AIS Turkey - Board Member

Oct 2019 - Jul 2020

Istanbul / Turkey

AIS is an artificiel intelligence society founded by students at Bahçeşehir University. After a while, the community grow all around the Turkey under the name of "AIS Turkey". Our goal was to ensure the development of artificial intelligence for the whole of Turkey. Besides the board of directors, I also worked as a web developer.

EKOBOT 2017

Izmir / Turkey

This Project was awarded the first prize in the robot contest with the theme "I Think Robotics" organized by the University of Bahcesehir and the french high school of Saint Benoit. Under the name of social responsibility project, we designed an automatic environmental robot.

Sep 2020 - Jul 2020

Education and Qualifications

Computer Enginnering

Oct 2019 - Present

Bahçeşehir University, Istanbul / Turkey

High School 2015 - 2019

The High School of Tevfik Fikret Izmir, Izmir / Turkey

Certificates

Google SDC - Certificate of Appreciation

May 2020

Apr 2020

Google DSC Bau

Programming in C++ Apr 2020

Udemy

HTML 101 Certificate

Turkcell

Turkcell	
Microsoft Student Partner Introduction to Al and Azure Cognitive Services Microsoft	Nov 2019
Microsoft Student Partner Introduction to Azure Microsoft	Nov 2019
Python 101 Certificate Turkcell	Nov 2019
Fermat Mathematics Conteset Başarı Belgesi University of Waterloo	2017

Skills

HTML5
CSS3
JavaScript
C++
Python

HTML5 & CSS3 202 Certificate

References

Berke Can ONGUN

Microsoft Learn Student
- Ambassador

Apr 2020

berkecan98.8@gmail.com